#### Contact

jasminestarr05@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/ jasmineswiseman (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

Nursing Healthcare BLS

### Languages

**English** 

### Certifications

Medical Surgical Registered Nurse BLS for Healthcare Providers ACLS

Registered Nurse

# Jasmine Wiseman, BSN, RN, CMSRN

Registered Nurse Clinician III at UVA Health System & Family Nurse Practitioner Student at the University of Virginia

Charlottesville, Virginia Area

## Summary

Hello! My name is Jasmine. I am a Registered Nurse with more than six years of experience in adult medsurg acute & intermediate care. I am currently in the Family Nurse Practitioner program at the University of Virginia. I have a passion for Women's/Adolescent Reproductive Health as well as Public Health. My goal is to educate my patients to be knowledgeable healthcare consumers so they can make informed medical decisions that work the best for them. "An ounce of prevention is worth a pound of cure."- Benjamin Franklin

## Experience

UVA Health System
Registered Nurse Clinician III
March 2016 - Present (4 years 5 months)
Charlottesville, Virginia Area

Caring for complex post-operative surgical patients on a 12 bed critical care intermediate care unit.

Performing charge nurse responsibilities including staff and patient assignments.

Nursing responsibilities and skills include: performing physical assessments, continuous EKG monitoring and rhythm interpretation, blood transfusion administration, titrating IV medications: Amiodarone, Diltiazem, Narcan, Nicardipine, Heparin, Insulin and Calcium, medication review and administration, burn, wound and ostomy care, chest tube management, central line and arterial line care, tracheostomy care, performing conscious sedation for procedures and wound care, and assisting with activities of daily living, Planning and implementation of patient care including: delegation of patient care, monitor and assess progress towards patient's goals, and communicate effectively between all professionals that assist in the patient's care.

Patient populations include: Surgical, Trauma, Burn, Transplants: Kidney, Liver, and Pancreas, Gastroenterology, Gynecology, Orthopedics, Spinal, Plastics, and Urology.

Augusta Health Registered Nurse July 2013 - March 2016 (2 years 9 months) Fishersville, Virginia

Caring for multiple pre-operative and post-operative surgical patients on a 24 bed acute care unit.

Performing charge nurse responsibilities including staff and patient assignments.

Nursing responsibilities and skills include: performing physical assessments, blood transfusion administration, medication review and administration, wound and ostomy care, chest tube management, central line care, and assisting with activities of daily living.

Planning and implementation of patient care including: delegation of patient care, monitor and assess progress towards patient's goals, and communicate effectively between all professionals that assist in the patient's care.

Patient populations include: Gastroenterology, Orthopedics, Spinal, Gynecology, Urology, Vascular, and HEENT.

Also floated to other units including: Joint Center, Medical Unit, Progressive Care Unit, Emergency Department, Skilled Care, Post Partem Obstetrics, Nursery and Pediatrics, and Psychiatry.

DuPont Community Credit Union Service Center Executive II June 2007 - July 2013 (6 years 2 months) Waynesboro, Virginia

Answered incoming calls to the credit union, transferred calls, transferred funds, opened new accounts and certificates of deposits, ordered checks, helped members troubleshoot with home banking login, verified deposits, conducted research on member's accounts, quoted mortgage and loan rates, knowledge of all credit union products and services, and sold products that met members needs while maintaining exceptional member service and confidentiality.

Sentara Martha Jefferson Intern February 2013 - March 2013 (2 months)

Charlottesville, Virginia

Cared for multiple patients on the medical/surgical unit. Performed physical assessments, medication administration, wound care, and assisted with activities of daily living.

## Education

University of Virginia

Master of Science - MS, Family Nurse Practitioner · (2018 - 2021)

James Madison University
Bachelor of Science (BS), RN to BSN · (2013 - 2015)

Blue Ridge Community College (Virginia)
Associate of Science (A.S.), Registered Nursing/Registered
Nurse · (2011 - 2013)

Blue Ridge Community College (Virginia)
Associate of Arts and Sciences (A.A.S.) (2007 - 2010)